module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'What area of the body is the duodenum located?', 
    a: 'Head',
    b: 'Stomach',
    c: 'Pelvis',
    d: 'Chest',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which brand of paper towels used the slogan "The Quicker Picker Upper!"?', 
    a: 'Brawny',
    b: 'Sparkle',
    c: 'Bounty',
    d: 'Scott',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who composed the 1877 romantic ballet "Swan Lake"?', 
    a: 'Tchaikovsky',
    b: 'Chopin',
    c: 'Wagner',
    d: 'Beethoven',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What audience measurement system is used for television programming?', 
    a: 'ESRB Ratings',
    b: 'Alexa Rankings',
    c: 'Pew Research Method',
    d: 'Nielsen Ratings',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'The Internet protocol suite is also known as ____.', 
    a: 'TCP/IP',
    b: 'UDP',
    c: 'IPv6',
    d: 'DNS',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which modern states did New Netherland encompass in the 17th century?', 
    a: 'NY and NJ',
    b: 'VA and WV',
    c: 'NC and SC',
    d: 'NH and VT',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is a vestigial-structure?', 
    a: 'Paper Clip',
    b: 'Human Appendix',
    c: 'Golgi-Body',
    d: 'Mucus Membrane',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What plane figure has five straight sides and five angles', 
    a: 'Trapezoid',
    b: 'Decagon',
    c: 'Pentagon',
    d: 'Heptagon',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who was the main antagonist in The Hunchback of Notre-Dame?', 
    a: 'Amos Slade',
    b: 'Quasimodo',
    c: 'Gaston',
    d: 'Claude Frollo',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who was the winner of the first season the reality show "Survivor"?', 
    a: 'Richard Hatch',
    b: 'Regis Philbin',
    c: 'Sue Hawk',
    d: 'John Cochran',
    answer: 'a'
  },
];